2500sz.co 2018-08-28

# Privacy Policy - 2500SZ

Privacy Policy for http://2500sz.co

The privacy of our visitors to http://2500sz.co is important to us.

At http://2500sz.co, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit http://2500sz.co, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files: As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons: We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on http://2500sz.co to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases,

#### Ads

#### Categories

#### Recent Posts

  * [How You Can Get Ready For An Inconvenience Free Adventure Holiday](http://2500sz.co/can-get-ready-inconvenience-free-adventure-holiday/)

#### Archives
